dhfl.com 2015-12-28

# DHFL Privacy Policy - Terms & Conditions

By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

From time to time we may reveal general statistical information about our Web site and visitors, such as number of visitors etc. Your trust and confidence are our highest priority.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. Notwithstanding the above we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless:

  * we have your permission
  * to provide products or services you’ve requested
  * circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or regulators or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure

We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our site. We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process or any combination there of.

Upon request, we will remove/block your personally identifiable information from our database, thereby canceling your registration. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

Your right to privacy is very important. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act responsibly. We believe this information should only be used to help us provide you with better service. That’s why we have put a policy in place to protect your personal information. Below is a summary of our policy.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our site.

We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process or any combination thereof.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. Notwithstanding the above we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless:

  * we have your permission
  * to provide products or services you’ve requested
  * circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or regulators or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure.

In general, when you visit our web site (“Site”) and access information you remain anonymous. There are, however, occasions where we request from you certain information such as your e-mail or mailing address. The purpose of our requesting such information is to be able to better understand your needs, and provide you with services that we believe may be valuable to you. Before we ask you for any such information, we will generally explain how this information will be used. We will not provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals without your permission. We may, however, provide such information to contractors providing services to us in relation to this Site or to our operations.

**PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY**

Upon request, we will remove / block your personally identifiable information from our database, thereby canceling your registration. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

We will take appropriate steps to protect your privacy in relation to your use of our Site. This Site may provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control such linked sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party sites.

**USE OF COOKIES**

Our Site uses a technology called cookies that may be used to provide you with specific information. A cookie is a small element of data that our Site may send to your computer. Any such cookie is typically stored on your computer’s hard drive and permits our Site to recognize you when you return to the Site. Our use of cookies helps us to provide you with a better experience during your use of our Site by allowing us to understand what areas of the Site are of interest to you. These cookies do not track your individual information.

Due to the rapidly evolving technologies on the Internet, we may occasionally update this policy. All revisions will be posted to this Site.
